All right, back for another one. Listen,
I'm going to talk about AI today. And
this is a topic we can't get away from.
We live in a culture right now in a
society where it's a polarizing topic.
Is AI something that is here for good?
Should we be using it in our businesses?
That's what I want to talk about today
is if you are a coach or a mentor, maybe
you've made your money in the past doing
services like writing or graphics design
or things like that and you're not quite
comfortable with using artificial
intelligence or you're like, I don't
want it to ruin my voice. I don't want
to give the the control of how I sound
to a robot. In this video, I want to
show you why I think that every business
owner should be using AI and the right
way to do so. Number one, chat GPT
changed everything when it comes to what
we think about artificial intelligence.
It can write, it can come up with ideas,
it can help solve problems, but it's not
the end all beall answer to everything
that we're dealing with. And artificial
intelligence comes in a number of
different ways. For instance, like this
car right now, this is a self-driving
Tesla that I am in right now.
and it is 100%
driving itself, taking me to my
destination. I just have to keep my eyes
on the road. And that's artificial
intelligence that's doing that. We live
in a world today where everything is
shifting in this direction for AI. Now,
you can fight it. You can say, well, I
don't want to AI to take over. As
business owners, if you are a business
owner,
I see AI as a as an assistant that you
can hire, that you can use that can help
you to build a business. And listen, I
know all the different things people say
like, "Yeah, sure. That sounds great
until you know it kicks you out of a job
or things like that." Can I tell you
this? I want you to think bigger and I
want you to think higher. And I want you
to think higher of yourself and your
ability to learn skills and your ability
to innovate.
If you can learn to use artificial
intelligence, it is no different than
hiring a team of people that is doing
your marketing for you. Like for this,
if I hired a chauffeur that drove me
around, this car is the same type of
thing like that. And so it gives you
time. It gives you the ability to do
stuff with your time, to buy back your
time at a very, very low cost, much
cheaper than if you were hiring people
to do that. And for most business owners
that I meet, they don't have the budget
to be able to hire a full-time marketing
team or a full-time staff to do stuff.
And so using AI to do all those things
is a benefit to you because it allows
you to focus on where your zone of
genius is, which is coming up with
ideas, which is coaching people, which
is communicating,
recording videos like this. For me, this
is where my genius comes from and what
builds my business. And so I can come up
with all the kinds of different reasons
or excuses why I can't do certain things
in my business. This is a great example
of this. Instead, I am going and running
an errand, and I'm like, "Okay, I can
actually record a YouTube video right
now, which is on my list of things to do
today. I don't need to wait three hours
when I get back in the office to be able
to do this." And I can be focused and I
can actually focus on my message and
share something with people that is
really going to be valuable with them. I
just did a coaching call today with a
with a client of mine. She is a writer
and she's made her living with writing.
And I told her, listen, using AI, now
that you're elevating yourself from
being an employee to an entrepreneur,
using artificial intelligence to help
you come up with ideas for your
marketing, how do you say something on
social media? How do I want to
communicate this on my bio? How do I
want to write the pages on my website? I
meet so many business owners today that
spend hours and hours and hours of their
time trying to figure out what to say
and how to say it the right way because
that's what they've been trained. They
have a pride thing that's prideful
that's attached to this. And they might
call it a spirit of excellence. They
might even call it a spirit of
excellence, but it is keeping them
playing small because they refuse to use
these tools that we have access to now
that can save them time, that can allow
them to test things more frequently,
that can allow them to get stuff out
there. I don't need to buy stock photos.
I don't need to go do a photo shoot.
Now, even for my business, I can use AI
to create incredible marketing photos,
incredible language for my website. I
can have it brainstorm and summarize my
coaching calls, and give me what's some
underlying issues or things that I can
help coach my clients in. I had a
situation with another client where like
I had been coaching him for about 2
months and just wasn't getting the
progress that I knew was possible for
him. So, I did a conversation with Chad
GPT and I said, "Listen, I have this
client. We're dealing with this. This is
what we're working through. Give me a
way to help him get some breakthrough."
And listen, the first response it gave
me wasn't the best. But I finally was
like, "You know what? I've tried all
that. Go deeper." And then literally the
next thing that it gave me was such a
perfect thing. This client finally got
progress in his business by me applying
what I got from the AI. If I had my
pride and ego that said, "Well, I gotta
be the coach that comes up with all the
great ideas. I can't let some robot come
up with good ideas for me without me
doing it."
My client wouldn't have been served at
that level. And I would want to make
sure that I can use all of the tools
that are available to me today to serve
my clients at the highest level. And so
for me, using AI helps me be a better
coach. It helps me be a better parent.
It helps me be a better a better leader.
It helps me be a better teacher. I've
been in this industry of marketing and
coaching online for almost 22 years. We
didn't have AI to do a lot of this
stuff.
And the strategies that I use come from
that experience combined with using
artificial intelligence. And I'm telling
you, as somebody who is skilled in this
industry, that knows how to make
content, that knows how to persuade
people to buy from me, that knows how to
create products and services that people
want and bring them into the marketplace
and make real finances from them,
multiple seven figures of finances in
business.
I'm using AI to help augment to attach
onto my own knowledge to amplify and to
save me time to save me effort so that I
can reach more people because that is
the definition of working smarter
not harder in my business. And so if you
are a business owner today, I implore
you, get a chat GPT account,
start using it. Start testing it out.
Start seeing
what you can do with it. Come up with
your your next marketing piece. Say,
"Listen, I have this product. I want to
brainstorm an idea for a marketing
product." Explain how you want to help
people. Have it come up with ideas for
this. If you go over to my website,
jeremiacowski.com, you can find a link
in the bio below, I have a link at the
top part of my website, the top
navigation part that says my top AI
prompts. And these are some of my best
AI prompts that have made us eight
figures in our businesses that we've
helped people build. This has helped my
clients make multiple eight figures per
year in their businesses. And it can
help you as well. And these are prompts
that I've actually put together that you
can use to brainstorm, to iterate, to
come up with ideas for your product, for
your service, for your marketing, how
you're going to communicate it with
people, how to say it, how to show up,
what do you put in your advertising,
what to put in your social media, what
kind of lead magnets to create, what
kind of language to use to persuade
people to become your client overall.
And so if you can learn how to do those
things the right way in your business,
this is going to help you go further
than you ever possibly imagined. Listen,
if you are a coach, if you are a mentor,
and you want to learn how to grow your
business using evergreen offers, using
AI, using copywriting, using the sales
skills that you need to be able to do
that, and you want me to help you, to
come alongside you, to show you how to
do that, click on the one of the links
in my bio, jump into my wealthy coach
academy program. This is where coaches
and mentors make the most amount of
money in their business. We are helping
them specifically get wealthy in their
business to know exactly what to do,
what steps to take, what moves to make,
and what's actually going to work for
them. And I promise you, you will see
results if you get in there. Try it out
for 14 days. We have a 14-day trial.
Click the link in the description below
and I'll see you in there. We'll talk
soon. Have a good one.